amazingregistry.com 2019-04-23

# Privacy Policy - AmazingRegistry.com

AmazingRegistry.com is committed to your right to privacy and to taking steps designed to secure your personal information. To earn your trust and confidence in our commitment, the intent of this policy is to fully disclose our privacy practices to you. We will only use your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

The AmazingRegistry.com website is owned and operated by Amazing Registry.com Inc. AmazingRegistry.com makes the registries of various retailers available through this website and also offers related products and services provided by other companies.

We encourage you to read the AmazingRegistry.com privacy policy, as well as those of the retailers you register with or purchase from, and of the other companies featured on our website, so you understand what types of personal information are collected and how this information may be used. AmazingRegistry.com and the retailers and other companies participating in this website are committed to collecting and using your information only in accordance with their respective privacy policies.

By using this website, you consent to the collection and use of your information as described in these Privacy Policies. 

As part of our Privacy Policy, we address the following:

  * The personal information we collect
  * With whom your information is shared and how it is used 
  * The choices you have about the collection and use of your information 
  * Your ability to access, update or correct your information 
  * The security measures we take to protect your personal information 
  * Additional information about online privacy and changes to our policy 

The personal information we collect

General. AmazingRegistry.com and its partners collect personal information necessary to provide you with customized products and services and to allow you to use the resources available on our, and our partner's websites, including the creation and maintenance of a Account and an online gift registry. Personal information includes, but is not limited to, name, physical address, email address, phone number, age and any other information that itself identifies or, when tied to the above information, may identify you as a specific individual. AmazingRegistry.com and its partners also collect information related to your event, including your event date, shower date, co-registrants and information relating to your gift registry and honeymoon. AmazingRegistry.com may also collect your contact information, and demographic information when you request certain information, products and services on our website.

Contests and Online Surveys. AmazingRegistry.com and its partners frequently sponsor contests to give you the opportunity to win great prizes. Your participation in these contests is entirely optional. Information we collect for such contests can include contact information and demographic information. AmazingRegistry.com also values the opinions and comments from all of our users, so we frequently conduct surveys online, via e-mail, or by telephone. Your participation in these surveys is entirely optional. Information we collect in online surveys will include general information on the use of our website and other demographic information, such as age and income bracket. Survey participants are anonymous unless otherwise stated in the survey.

Cookies. "Cookies" are small pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookie files are used to better understand how you go through our website so we may tailor your experience at our website. Cookies are also used to tell us whether you have visited our website previously, and to help us determine whether you came to our website from a particular Internet link or banner advertisement. Cookies can also be used to help you to save and retrieve passwords and other information and preferences you use on our website, saving you from having to re-enter this information upon every visit to our website. Cookies cannot and will not be used by us to retrieve any personal information about you from your computer that you have not previously and voluntarily provided to us. However, cookies may also be received when you link to our partners' websites or when you view or click on banner advertisements served by our outside advertising company and we do not have control over how they use this information. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block them in the future. However, most of our features will not function if you do not accept cookies. 

Analysis. We have partnered with a third party, Google Analytics, to assist us in better understanding how people use our site. Google Analytics analyzes the information collected on our website through cookies and returns it to us through a secure web connection. We use the information to help us understand your interests in our website and how to better serve you. 

With whom your information is shared and how it is used 

When you provide information to AmazingRegistry.com or its partners as described above, some of the information is stored in our and some of our partners' databases. Such information is used by AmazingRegistry.com in accordance with this Privacy Policy and by our partners in accordance with their policies. Information we collect is used by us (i) to tailor your experience at our website, (ii) to show you content we think you might be interested in, (iii) to display content according to your preferences, (iv) to notify you of important functionality changes, new AmazingRegistry.com services and other noteworthy news items about us, our partners, and our vendors, (v) to send you information, special offers and other promotional materials about AmazingRegistry.com, our partners and our vendors, and/or (vi) if it becomes necessary to contact you.

In addition, to allow you to use some of our features and/or to fulfill your requests and/or orders (including online gift registry and online shopping), information we collect will also be shared with our partners and other third parties, such as product suppliers, airlines, car rental agencies, and travel agencies. Finally, we may also share your personal information with other providers of products and services, we think may be of interest to you. Although this Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices or policies of any such partners, vendors or third parties, we generally require all of our partners agree not to use your personal information, except as fully disclosed to you or authorized by you.

Any information we collect may be shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. In addition, we may from time to time hire a third party to act on our behalf for projects such as market research surveys, contest entry processing, and other distribution, and we will provide information to these third parties specifically for use in connection with these projects. The information we provide to such third parties will be protected by a confidentiality agreement that will obligate the third party to use such information solely to complete the specific project.

In addition to the circumstances described above, we may disclose your information if required to do so by law, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authorities, or in the good faith belief disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable, including (without limitation) when we have reason to believe disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities. Information stored on our servers may also be transferred to a third party acquiring or merging with the company. However, any such third party shall be required to use such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

The choices you have about the collection and use of your information 

AmazingRegistry.com gives you a choice about how we use your personal information. Our website provides you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us at the point where we request information from you. In other words, if you don't want to receive such communications, just let us know at the time you provide such information. In addition, we will also provide you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future marketing communications from us by clicking on the opt-out link at the bottom of e-mail communications. 

Your choices with respect to personal information provided by you or us to partners, vendors, and other third parties is governed by the privacy policies of such partners, vendors, and other third parties. We encourage you to read their privacy policies and follow their instructions with respect to the use of your information. AmazingRegistry.com reserves the right to limit registration to those who will accept emails and to those who will provide the requested information.

Your ability to access, update or correct your information 

At any time, you can view, update, or delete all of the information contained in your Account, or Gift Registry by logging in to your account and following the appropriate links or by clicking ‘Contact us’ and selecting ‘Remove my registry’. Your account log-in can be easily accessed by visiting our website at www.AmazingRegistry.com . In addition, you can update or delete such information by contacting our customer service department by email at help@AmazingRegistry.com. However, even if you delete or change some personal information in our registration database, it may still be stored on our, or other third party, databases (including those kept for archival purposes).

The security measures we take to protect your personal information

When you register for certain online gift registries, you will have the opportunity (depending on which partner you are registering with) to select whether you wish to make your online registry private. If you do not elect to make your gift registry or other, anyone visiting our website will be able to search for your registry by using first and/or last names and wedding dates (and on some pages, city or state).

Additional information about online privacy and changes to our policy 

Please be aware our website has advertisements and links to other websites that may collect personal information about you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices or policies of such websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of all such websites, as their policies may be materially different from our Privacy Policy. Any material changes in the way we use personal information will be described in future versions of this Privacy Policy. Of course, you may always submit concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or our privacy practices to our Customer Service Center at help@AmazingRegistry.com. Please reference the Privacy Policy in your subject line. We will attempt to respond to all reasonable concerns or inquiries within five business days of receipt.

Contact Us 

By E-mail: help@amazingregistry.com

By Phone: 800-220-5802
